Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs 5917 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Railex strike - 9/1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  7 photographs; 2 slides
- A. Philip Randolph (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Regina Negotiations - 11/1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Regina negotiations - 11/1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Regina Shop Members at work (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Regina strike - 11/1962 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Renaming 7th Ave. (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Rent Control Demonstration (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Reporter, Photo Used (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Retire Members Medicare Demonstration (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Retirees, 3/1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Retirees Center - James Pagano (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Retirees Delegation to Albany - 4/1969 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Retirees - FLM Jt. Board (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Retirees Rally - District 65 - 10/1982 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Reuther, Walter (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Reuther, Walter (negative) (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Paul Rosen (Box 11, Folder 19)
  Empty
- Rodino visits to Newark Shops - 5/29/1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Rodino visits to Newark Shops - 5/29/1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Romero Strike - Feb-March, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Franklin D. Roosevelt (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Roosevelt, Franklin D. (negative) (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Alex, Rose (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Rosenblatt, I Thompson (Box 11, Folder 26)
- S- (Box 11, Folder 27)
- S- (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Sack's 5th Ave. Picketing (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Sack's 5th Ave. Picketing (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Sack's 5th Ave. Picketing (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Ben Salzman (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Saltzman, major General Charles (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Max Salzman (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Mike Scarpelli (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Jack Schneider (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Jack Schneider - Furriers Joint Council (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Jack Scheider - Furriers Joint Council (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Senior Citizens Rally - 10/22/1969 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Seton Leather Co. - Ratification - 3/9/1972 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Jacqueline Sharpe (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Shop photos (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Shorter Work Week (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Dmitri Shostakovitch (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Ng. Slater (Box 11, Folder 45)
- FLM Members at work - N G. Slater (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Gladstone Smith (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Soldiers - World War II (Box 11, Folder 48)
  21 photographs
- Soldiers WWII (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Soldiers WWII (negative) (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Solidarity Day - 9/19/1981 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Solidarity Day - 9/19/1981 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- South African Demonstration - 11/30/1978 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Spanish Trade Unionists visit to set on Ocean Leather - 8/4/1986 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Sports (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Sports (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Sports (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Sports/Recreation (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Steel Partition Meeting - 12/23/1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Stevens Gimbles - 12/27/1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Stevenson Market Rally, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- George Stofsky (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Stofsky-Jasper Bon Voyage Dinner - 5/1964 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Stofsky-Jasper Bon Voyage Dinner (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Leon Straus - American Youth Congress Rally (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Leon and Bernard Straus - 7/29/1983 - 8/1/1983 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Street Scenes (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Strike Photo, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Strikers WWII (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Strikes (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Strikes and Pickets (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Strikes/Pickets (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Superior Pet Grievances (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Superior Pet Products - Members at work (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Superior Pet Products - members at work (Box 12, Folder 20)
- T- (Box 12, Folder 21)
- James Talbenor (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Tannery Visit (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Glenn Taylor - Candidate for BP 1948, Progressive Party (Box 12, Folder 24)
- TEC - Cast meeting and Strike - April 1988 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Tenant Delegation - Albany - 2/14/1951 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Tetley Tea - Members at work (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Tetley Tea Strike - 8/1977 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Transit Fare Picket Line (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Tubari Picketing - Fall - 1987 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Press Conference to Announce Tubari picketing (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Union Label Show - June, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- United Foods and Commercial Workers (UFCW) - Lane Kirkland + Secretary of Labor (Film Staff) (Sheraton Hotel - NYC (Carter Mobilization - 1980)) Irving Stern (Box 12, Folder 33)
- United Fur Cutters Members at work (Box 12, Folder 34)
- United Mechanics - 150 - Meeting - 3/29/1979 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- United Mechanics - ISO - Meeting - 3/29/1979 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- United Mineral Strike - 1964 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- U.S. Blindsitch Contract and Strike 3/1982 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- U.S. Blindstitch - Members at work (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Unused photos (Box 12, Folder 40)
- V- (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Voter Registration (Box 12, Folder 42)
- W- (Box 12, Folder 43)
- W- (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Henry Wallace (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Wallace Election Campaign, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Germaine Wasserman (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Archie Waters (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Irwin C. Watson (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Gladston Smith-Parnes Weinberg (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Welfare Fund Trustees (DUP) (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Welfare Fund Trustees (DUP) (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Welfare Fund Trustees (DUP) (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Welfare Fund Trustees (DUP) (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Welfare Strike, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Wellsboro Strike (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Wedemeyer, Joseph [8x10 Negative] (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Wedemeyer, Joseph (Box 13, Folder 8)
  was ff 7A; 1 photograph
- White Lake Lodge (Box 13, Folder 9)
  was ff 8; 1 photograph
- White Lake Lodge 1954 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  was ff 9; 7 photographs
- White Lake Aerial Shots (Box 13, Folder 11)
  was ff 10; 4 photographs
- White Lake Lodge - Outing (Box 13, Folder 12)
  was ff 11; 3 photographs
- Wilbur (Sonny) Wiggins (Box 13, Folder 13)
  was ff 12; 2 photographs
- Doxey Wilkerson (Box 13, Folder 14)
  was ff 13; 2 photographs
- Wilmington Chemical Photos - December, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  was ff 14; 3 photographs
- Wilmington Chemical Strike 3/78, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  was ff 15; 1 photograph
- Joseph Winogradsky (Box 13, Folder 17)
  was ff 16; 5 photographs
- Joseph Winosgrady - Asst. Mgr. - Furriers Joint Council (Box 13, Folder 18)
  was ff 17; 9 photographs
- Secretary of Labor Willard Wirtz (Box 13, Folder 19)
  was ff 18; 1 photograph
- Women's Activities (Box 13, Folder 20)
  was ff 19; 12 photographs
- Women's Committee (Box 13, Folder 21)
  was ff 20; 4 photographs
- Women Leaders & Programs (Box 13, Folder 22)
  was ff 21; 5 photographs
- Bernard T. Woolis (Box 13, Folder 23)
  was ff 22; 3 photographs
- Woolis Testimonial Dinner 6/17/71, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  was ff 23; 4 photographs
- Woolworth Demonstration (Box 13, Folder 25)
  was ff 24; 5 photographs
- Workers (Box 13, Folder 26)
  was ff 25; 10 photographs
- WWII Activities (Box 13, Folder 27)
  was ff 26; 16 photographs
- WWII Activities (Box 13, Folder 28)
  was ff 27; 12 photographs
- WWII Activities (Box 13, Folder 29)
  was ff 28; 13 photographs
- WWII Rally - Second Front (Box 13, Folder 30)
  was ff 29; 17 photographs
- Fur Industry - World War II War Bond Rally - Fiorello La Guardia, Milton Berle (Box 13, Folder 31)
  was ff 30; 1 photograph
- Workers (Box 13, Folder 32)
  was ff 31; 10 photographs
- Workers (Box 13, Folder 33)
  was ff 32; 10 photographs
- Y- (Box 13, Folder 34)
  was ff 33; 1 photograph
- Youth Activities (Box 13, Folder 35)
  was ff 34; 17 photographs
- Youth Activities (Box 13, Folder 36)
  was ff 35; 8 photographs
- Youth Activities (Box 13, Folder 37)
  was ff 36; 9 photographs
- Youth March for Jobs 4/78, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  was ff 37; 5 photographs
- Dale Zysman (Box 13, Folder 39)
  was ff 38; 1 photograph
- New Union press from Tempo (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Tempo - 12/1967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Tempo - 12/1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Tempo - 12/1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Tempo - 12/1967 - (negative) (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Tempo - #1 - 2/1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Tempo #2 - Feb. 1968 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Temp #2 - Feb. 1968 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Tempo - 2/1968 (negative) (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Tempo - April 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Tempo - April, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Temp - April, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Tempo - April, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Tempo - 6/1968 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Tempo - 6/1968 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Tempo - 6/1968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Tempo - Dec. 1968 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Tempo - 12/1968 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Tempo - Feb, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Tempo - Feb. 1969 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Tempo - Feb. 1969 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Tempo - Feb., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Tempo - April 1969 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Tempo - April, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Tempo - June 1969 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Tempo - June - 1969 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Tempo- June 1969 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Tempo - October 1969 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Tempo - October, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Tempo - 12/1969 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Tempo - December - 1969 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Tempo - Feb. 1970 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Tempo - 2/ 1970 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Tempo - 4/1970 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Tempo - 4/1970 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Tempo - 7/70, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 34; 14 photographs
- Tempo - 7/70, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 35; 10 photographs
- Tempo - 7/70, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 36; 9 photographs
- Tempo - 12/1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 37; 8 photographs
- Tempo - 12/1970 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 38; 13 photographs
- Tempo - 2/71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 38; 7 photographs
- Tempo-2/71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 40; 12 photographs
- Tempo - 4/71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 41; 9 photographs
- Tempo - 4/71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 42; 10 photographs
- Tempo - 4/71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 43; 9 photographs
- Tempo - 4/71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 44; 10 photographs
- Tempo - 4/71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 45; 9 photographs
- Tempo - October-November, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 46; 10 photographs
- Tempo - October-November, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 47; 10 photographs
- Tempo - October-November, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 48; 5 photographs
- Tempo - 12/71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 49; 11 photographs
- Tempo - 12/71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 50; 7 photographs
- Tempo - 12/71, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 51; 12 photographs
- Tempo - 2/72, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 52; 12 photographs
- Tempo - 2/72, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 53; 16 photographs
- Tempo - 4/72, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 54; 16 photographs
- Tempo - 4/72, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 55; 12 photographs
- Tempo - 6/72, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 56; 22 photographs
- Tempo - 6/72, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 57; 12 photographs
- Tempo - 6/72, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 58; 18 photographs
- Tempo - 10/72, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 59; 12 photographs
- Tempo - 10/72, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 60; 13 photographs
- Tempo - 12/72, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 61; 21 photographs
- Tempo-2/73, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 62; 17 photographs
- Tempo - 4/73, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 63; 19 photographs
- Tempo - 6/73, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  collection re-organized - was box 14, ff 64; 10 photographs
- Tempo - 6/1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Tempo - 6/1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Tempo - 6/1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Tempo - 10/1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Tempo - 10/1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Tempo - 12/1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Tempo - 2/1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Tempo - 2/1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Tempo - 4/1974 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Tempo - 4/1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Tempo - 6/1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Tempo - 6/1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Tempo - 6/1974 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Tempo - 10/1974 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Tempo - 10/1974 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Tempo - 10/1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Tempo - 12/1974 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Tempo - 12/1974 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Tempo - 2/1975 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Tempo - 2/1975 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Tempo - 4/1975 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Tempo - 4/1975 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Tempo - 6/1975 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Tempo - 6/1975 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Tempo - 10/1975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Tempo - 10/1975 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Tempo - 12/1975 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Tempo - 12/1975 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Tempo - 12/1975 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Tempo - 2/1976 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  36 photographs
- Tempo - 4/1976 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Tempo - 4/1976 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Tempo - 6/1976 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Tempo - 6/1976 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Tempo - 10/1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Tempo - 10/1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Tempo - 10/1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Tempo - 12/1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Tempo - 12/1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  29 photographs
- Tempo - 2/1977 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Tempo - 2/1977 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Tempo - Arp.-May 1977 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  22 photographs
- Tempo - Apr.-May 1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Tempo - 6/1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Tempo - 6/1977 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Tempo - 12/1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Tempo - 10/1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Tempo - 10/1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Tempo - 12/1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Tempo - 12/1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Tempo - 12/1978 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Tempo - 2/1978 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Tempo - 4/1978 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Tempo - 4/1978 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Tempo - 4/1978 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Tempo - June-July, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Tempo - June-July 1978 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Tempo - June-July 1978 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Tempo - 10/1978 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Tempo - 10/1978 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Tempo - 12/1978 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Tempo - 12/1978 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Tempo - 2-3/1978, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Tempo - 2-3/1979 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Tempo - 2-3/79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 31
- Tempo - 4-5/79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 32
- Tempo - 4-5/79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 33; 19 photographs
- Tempo - 6-7/79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 34; 13 photographs
- Tempo - 6-7/79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 35; 19 photographs
- Tempo - 5-6/79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 36; 12 photographs
- Tempo - 10-11/79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 37; 13 photographs
- Tempo - 10-11/79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 38; 18 photographs
- Tempo - 10-11/79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 39; 12 photographs
- Tempo - 10-11/79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 40; 13 photographs
- Tempo - March-April, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 41; 8 photographs
- Tempo - 3-4/80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 42; 17 photographs
- Tempo - 5-6/80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 43; 10 photographs
- Tempo - 5-6/80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 44; 26 photographs
- Tempo - 5-6/80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 45; 17 photographs
- Tempo - 7-8/80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 46; 14 photographs
- Tempo - 7-8/80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 47; 14 photographs
- Tempo - 7-8/80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 48; 9 photographs
- Tempo - 7-8/80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 49; 13 photographs
- Tempo - 10/80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 50; 14 photographs
- Tempo - 10/80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 51; 15 photographs
- Tempo - December, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 52; 11 photographs
- Tempo - December, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 53; 15 photographs
- Tempo - December, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 54; 21 photographs
- Tempo - February, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 55; 10 photographs
- Tempo - February, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 56; 16 photographs
- Tempo - February, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 57; 14 photographs
- Tempo - February, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 58; 19 photographs
- Tempo - February, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 59; 11 photographs
- Tempo - May/June, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 60; 13 photographs
- Tempo - Many/June, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 61; 13 photographs
- Tempo - May/June, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 62; 20 photographs
- Tempo - May/June, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 63; 17 photographs
- Tempo - July/August, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 64; 18 photographs
- Tempo - July/August, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 65; 15 photographs
- Tempo - July-August, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 66; 9 photographs
- Tempo - July/August, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 67; 11 photographs
- Tempo - July/August, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 68; 20 photographs
- Tempo - November, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 69; 19 photographs
- Tempo - November, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 70; 16 photographs
- Tempo - November, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 71; 11 photographs
- Tempo - November, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 72; 12 photographs
- Tempo - August/September, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 73; 20 photographs
- Tempo - August/September, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 74; 13 photographs
- Tempo - August/September, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 75; 17 photographs
- Tempo - December, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 76; 22 photographs
- Tempo - December, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 77; 14 photographs
- Tempo - 12/82, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 78; 13 photographs
- Tempo - February, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 79; 19 photographs
- Tempo - February, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 80; 12 photographs
- Tempo - February, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 81; 16 photographs
- Tempo - 4/83, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 82; 15 photographs
- Tempo - April, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 83; 19 photographs
- Tempo - June, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 84; 21 photographs
- Tempo - June, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 85; 16 photographs
- Tempo - 10/83, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 86; 18 photographs
- Tempo - 10/83, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 87; 23 photographs
- Tempo - December, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  collection re-organized - was box 15, ff 88; 35 photographs
- Misc. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 1; 4 photographs
- AAA Rack Co. Shop Mtg. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 2; 2 photographs
- Able Steel Mtg. - 4/16/75, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 3; 1 photograph
- Abonddo Luncheon - 9/1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 4; 2 photographs
- James Adkins (Box 20, Folder 5)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 5; 1 photograph
- AFI Washington Lobby - 3/1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 6; 2 photographs
- NYS AFL-CIO Convention - 8/1980 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 7; 1 photograph
- Alaska Lands Meetings - 11/20/1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 8; 4 photographs
- Allegheny Division Board Mtg. 11/1969 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 9; 1 photograph
- Alleghent Division Board Mtg. 10/24/1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 10; 28 negatives
- Allegheny Division Board - 4/1972 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 11; 2 photographs
- Allegheny Division Board - 6/2/1973 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 12; 6 photographs
- Allegheny Division Board - 6/7/1975 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 13
- Allegheny Division Board - 6/26/1976 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 14; 6 photographs
- Allegheny Division Conference - 6/11/1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 15; 20 photographs
- Allegheny Board Meeting - 6/1978 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 16; 8 photographs
- Allegheny Division Board Meeting - 6/7/1980 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 17; 7 photographs
- Allegheny Division Board Meeting - 6/6/1981 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 18; 12 photographs
- Allegheny Division Board Meeting - 6/19/1982 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 19; 11 photographs
- Allegheny Division Class - 2/20/1982 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 20; 3 photographs
- Allegheny Division Board - 6/4/1983 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 21; 7 photographs
- Allegheny Division Board Meeting - 6/2/1984 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 22; 1 photograph
- Allegheny Division Board Meeting - 6/1/1985 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 23; 4 photographs
- Allegheny Division Board Meeting - 6/7/1986 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  collection re-organized - was box 17, ff 24; 23 photographs
- Alpha Chemical Contract (Box 20, Folder 25)